# **AUBREY RIGBY**

Ellensburg, WA 98926

Phone: (509) 949-9025 | Email: aubrey.rigby@gmail.com

LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/in/aubrey-rigby | GitHub: https://github.com/aubrey-rigby

Portfolio: https://aubrey-rigby.github.io/full-stack-developer/

# **SUMMARY**

Full-stack web developer passionate about supporting small and local businesses. Experienced in working with and managing teams. Motivated by ongoing learning and personal growth. Excited to employ skills as a web developer while continuing to adapt to new technologies, developments, and user preferences.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL

Tools: GitHub, Heroku, VSCode, Bootstrap, Node.js, JQuery, React, Handlebars, MySQL, MongoDB, APIs, Express.js,

Mongoose, Sequelize, React

# **EXPERIENCE**

Fiscal Analyst I 2021 – Present

## **Central Washington University**

Ellensburg, WA

- Reconciled banking and accounting statements to ensure accuracy of reporting.
- Investigated the source and purpose of various gifts to steward the funds and uphold donor intent.
- Leveraged Blackbaud Financial Edge and Raiser's Edge SQL database systems to input, retrieve, and analyze data related to donors and financials.
- Responded to dynamic and complex daily assignments.

Office Assistant Lead 2019 –2021

#### **Central Washington University**

Ellensburg, WA

- Developed of a number of university webpages in Central's 2019 web theme with a focus on accessibility and brand standardization.
- Led the development of the database for campus COVID-19 contact tracing.
- Adapted daily to the challenges and tasks at hand.
- Recognized twice for service excellence through the Wildcat Way spotlight.

#### **Management Associate II**

Hertz

2018 – 2019 Yakima. WA

Protected customer information and mitigated fraudulent transactions.

- Compiled weekly reports on Excel spreadsheets and uploaded them to Microsoft Teams.
- Ensured fleet of vehicles was well maintained.

## **PROJECTS**

# The Smoking Gun

Repository: <a href="https://github.com/UWB-Bandits/the-smoking-gun">https://github.com/UWB-Bandits/the-smoking-gun</a>

Deployed: https://the-smoking-gun.herokuapp.com/

A customizable, digital bullet journal where users can store different kinds of information all in one place. Built mobile-first, this application will allow users to stay organized both at home and on the go.

- Created application branding guidelines and refactored code to standardize brand across all pages.
- Led development of list, habit tracker, and journal entry features.
- Designed a mobile-first user interface with a focus on accessibility.
- Collaborated with a team to develop concept and functional application using Kanban system.
- Monitored deployed application and addressed deployment bugs.
- Tested and standardized code through Travis CI.

Utilized: React, MongoDB, Mongoose, Axios, Express, Material-UI, Firebase, FullCalendar, Chart.js, Gravatar, Geolocation, various APIs.

# gifNjelly

Repository: <a href="https://github.com/TommyWillen/gifNjelly">https://github.com/TommyWillen/gifNjelly</a>
Deployed: <a href="https://mighty-fjord-82642.herokuapp.com">https://mighty-fjord-82642.herokuapp.com</a>

Users are able to caption gifs that are currently trending. They can then vote on previously created captions.

- Integrated data from a MySQL database into functional and responsive user interface
- Collaborated on backend development with a focus on Sequalize.
- Cooperated with a team through GitHub version control system.
- Solved roadblocks through research and team communication.

Utilized: SweetAlert, Handlebars, Giphy API, Express, Sequelize, MySQL, Passport, BCrypt, and Axios.

#### **React Employee Directory**

Repository: <a href="https://github.com/aubrey-rigby/react-employee-directory">https://github.com/aubrey-rigby/react-employee-directory</a>
Deployed: <a href="https://aubrey-rigby.github.io/react-employee-directory">https://aubrey-rigby.github.io/react-employee-directory</a>

Application utilizes randomuser.me to populate an employee directory. Users are able to sort or search by name, phone number, or email of employees.

- Leveraged React components to easily respond to user interaction and inputs.
- Independently developed both frontend and backend as the sole developer.
- Exceeded project requirements and expectations.
- Applied Bootstrap framework for responsive user interface.

Utilized: React, JSX, Axios, Bootstrap, randomuser.me.

### **EDUCATION**

Bootcamp Certificate: 2021 University of Washington, Seattle, WA

Completed intensive 24-week program focused on building dynamic web programs.

**Bachelor's Degree, Business Administration: 2017** University of Washington, Bothell, WA Graduated Magna Cum Laude with concentrations in Marketing and Retail Management.